Register of the John R. Chaisson Papers, 1940-1975.
Hoover Institution Archives
John R. Chaisson Papers,
1940-1975.
73066
Chaisson, John R., 1916-1972.
17 manuscript boxes, 9 envelopes, 20 phonotapes (10 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, diaries, appointment books, speeches and writings, notes, reports, memoranda, oral history transcript, sound recordings, photographs, and printed matter, relating to manpower and budgetary requirements of the U.S. Marine Corps, the Vietnamese Conflict, and U.S. Marine Corps activities during World War II, in China during 1948-1949, in Korea during 1953-1954, and in Vietnam during 1966-1968.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1973.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
United States. Marine Corps--Officers.; Korean War, 1950-1953.; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--China.; China.; China--History--Civil War, 1945-1949.; United States--Armed Forces.; Phonotapes.
Biographical Note.
1916, September 27 Born, Swampscott, Massachusetts
1939 A.B., Harvard University
1942-1945, 1953-1954 Assigned to 1st Marine Division
1966-1968 Assigned to service in Vietnam
1971 Promoted to Lieutenant General, USMC
1971-1972 Chief of Staff, U.S. Marine Corps
Container List
- Letters to Family, 1940-1945. (Box No. 1.)
  Letters from John R. Chaisson to his parents, arranged chronologically.
  - October 31, 1940, Quantico, Virginia (Box 1.)
  - November 2, 1940, Quantico, Virginia
  - November 5, 1940, Quantico, Virginia
  - Undated, Sunday, Quantico, Virginia
  - November 24, 1940, Quantico, Virginia
  - December 7, 1940, Quantico, Virginia
  - Undated, Sunday, Quantico Virginia
  - January 13, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - January 13, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - January 20, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - February 10, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - Undated, Tuesday, Quantico, Virginia
  - March 17, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - March 24, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - April 8, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - April 29, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - May 5, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - May 13, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - May 28, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - June 25, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - June 26, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - July 2, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - August 18, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - August 28, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - September 10, 1941, Quantico, Virginia
  - October 7, 1941, Norlina, North Carolina
  - October 9, 1941, Parris Island, South Carolina
  - October 14, 1941, Parris Island, South Carolina
  - October 27, 1941, Parris Island, South Carolina
  - November 10, 1941, New River, North Carolina
  - November 15, 1941, New River, North Carolina
  - November 24, 1941, New River, North Carolina
  - December 1, 1941, New River, North Carolina
  - December 10, 1941, New River, North Carolina
  - January 24, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - February 13, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - February 24, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - March 5, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - March 30, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - April 1, 1942, New River, North Carolina
  - April 6, 1942, El Paso, Texas
  - April 7, 1942
  - April 12, 1942, San Diego, California
  - April 30, 1942, Pago Pago Harbor
  - May 19, 1942, Pago Pago Harbor
  - June 6, 1942, Wallis Island
  - June 24, 1942, Wallis Island
  - July 31, 1942, Wallis Island
  - August 7, 1942, Wallis Island
  - August 28, 1942, Apia, Western Samoa
  - September 7, 1942, U.S.S. Jackson
  - September 24, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - October 17, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - November 12, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - December 1, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - December 14, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - December 18, 1942, Guadalcanal Island
  - January 22, 1943, Melbourne, Australia
  - February 20, 1943, enroute to San Francisco
  - April 30, 1943
  - May 20, 1943
  - June 16, 1943
  - June 19, 1943
  - June 21, 1943
  - July 7, 1943
  - July 23, 1943
  - August 23, 1943
  - August 28, 1943
  - September 22, 1943
  - October 1, 1943
  - October 11, 1943
  - October 17, 1943
  - October 20, 1943
  - October 30, 1943
  - November 8, 1943
  - November 26, 1943
  - November 30, 1943
  - December 18, 1943
  - January 7, 1944
  - January 21, 1944
  - January 26, 1944
  - February 16, 1944
  - February 23, 1944
  - March 2, 1944
  - March 15, 1944
  - April 1, 1944
  - April 20, 1944
  - May 8, 1944
  - May 11, 1944
  - May 15, 1944
  - May 23, 1944
  - June 18, 1944
  - July 1, 1944
  - July 8, 1944
  - August 2, 1944
  - August 20, 1944
  - August 31, 1944
  - September 6, 1944
  - September 22, 1944
  - September 27, 1944
  - October 5, 1944
  - October 24, 1944
  - January 2, 1945, Quantico, Virginia
  - January 12, 1945, Quantico, Virginia
  - March 6, 1945, Quantico, Virginia
  - May 7, 1945, Washington, D.C.
- Letters to Mrs. John R. Chaisson, 1948-1968. (Box No. 2-7.)
  Letters from John R. Chaisson to his wife, arranged chronologically.
  - June 7, 1948, San Francisco (Box 2.)
  - June 12, 1948, San Francisco
  - June 14, 1948, Hawaii
  - June 16, 1948, Guam
  - June 17, 1948, Guam
  - June 23, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - June 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - June 26, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - June 28, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - June 29, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 3, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 7, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 8, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 13, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 16, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 18, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 19, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 21, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 22, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 25, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 28, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 29, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 31, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - July 31, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 2, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 6, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 7, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 8, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 9, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 13, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 16, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 17, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 18, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 19, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 21, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 22, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 23, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - August 26, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 3, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 4, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 6, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 7, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 8, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 9, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 11, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 13, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 16, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 17, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 19, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 21, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 23, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 25, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 26, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 28, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 29, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - September 30, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 2, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 3, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 4, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 6, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 8, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 9, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 11, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 14, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 17, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 21, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 23, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 25, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 28, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 29, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 30, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - October 30, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 2, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 3, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 4, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 6, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 7, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 11, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 14, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 16, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 17, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 19, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 21, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 22, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 23, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 26, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 28, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - November 30, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 1, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 2, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 3, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 4, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 5, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 6, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 8, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 9, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 10, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 11, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 12, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 13, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 14, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 15, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 16, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 18, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 19, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 20, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 22, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 24, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 25, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 26, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 27, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 29, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 30, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - December 31, 1948, Tsing Tao
  - January 1, 1949, Tsing Tao (Box 3.)
  - January 2, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 3, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 6, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 7, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 8, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 9, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 10, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 11, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 12, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 13, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 14, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 15, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 16, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 17, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 18, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 19, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 20, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 21, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 22, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 23, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 26, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 28, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 29, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 30, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 30, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - January 30, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - February 14, 1949, San Diego
  - February 21, 1949, Telegram, San Diego
  - February 22, 1949, San Diego
  - February 28, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 1, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 3, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 4, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 5, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 7, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 8, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 10, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 11, 1949, Camp Pendleton
  - March 13, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - March 15, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - March 17, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - March 19, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - March 22, 1949, Tsing Tao
  - October 19, 1953, Washington, D.C.
  - November 22, 1953, San Francisco
  - November 24, 1953, San Francisco
  - November 26, 1953, Hawaii
  - November 28, 1953, Guam
  - November 29, 1953, Atsugi, Japan
  - November 30, 1953, Itomi, Japan
  - December 3, 1953, Korea
  - December 3, 1953, Korea
  - December 6, 1953, Korea
  - December 6, 1953, Korea
  - December 7, 1953, Korea
  - December 8, 1953, Korea
  - December 12, 1953, Korea
  - December 13, 1953, Korea
  - December 14, 1953, Korea
  - December 15, 1953, Korea
  - December 18, 1953, Korea
  - December 19, 1953, Korea
  - December 20, 1953, Korea
  - December 21, 1953, Korea
  - December 23, 1953, Korea
  - December 24, 1953, Korea
  - December 25, 1953, Korea
  - December 26, 1953, Korea
  - December 27, 1953, Korea
  - December 29, 1953, Korea
  - December 30, 1953, Korea
  - January 1, 1954, Korea
  - January 2, 1954, Korea
  - January 3, 1954, Korea
  - January 4, 1954, Korea
  - January 6, 1954, Korea
  - January 7, 1954, Korea
  - January 8, 1954, Korea
  - January 10, 1954, Korea
  - January 11, 1954, Korea
  - January 11, 1954, Korea
  - January 13, 1954, Korea
  - January 14, 1954, Korea
  - January 15, 1954, Korea
  - January 17, 1954, Korea
  - January 17, 1954, Korea
  - January 18, 1954, Korea
  - January 19, 1954, Korea
  - January 21, 1954, Korea
  - January 22, 1954, Korea
  - January 23, 1954, Korea
  - January 24, 1954, Korea
  - January 25, 1954, Korea
  - January 25, 1954, Korea
  - January 26, 1954, Korea
  - January 28, 1954, Korea
  - January 29, 1954, Korea
  - January 31, 1954, Korea
  - February 1, 1954, Korea
  - February 3, 1954, Korea
  - February 4, 1954, Korea
  - February 5, 1954, Korea
  - February 6, 1945, Korea
  - February 7, 1954, Korea
  - February 8, 1954, Korea
  - February 9, 1954, Korea
  - February 10, 1954, Korea
  - February 12, 1954, Korea
  - February 13, 1954, Korea
  - February 14, 1954, Korea
  - February 16, 1954, Korea
  - February 17, 1954, Korea
  - February 19, 1954, Korea
  - February 20, 1954, Korea
  - February 21, 1954, Korea
  - February 23, 1954, Korea
  - February 24, 1954, Korea
  - February 26, 1954, Korea
  - February 28, 1954, Korea
  - March 1, 1954, Korea
  - March 2, 1954, Korea
  - March 3, 1954, Korea
  - March 5, 1954, Korea
  - March 11, 1954, Korea
  - March 14, 1954, Korea
  - March 14, 1954, Korea
  - March 15, 1954, Korea
  - March 16, 1954, Korea
  - March 17, 1954, Korea
  - March 19, 1954, Korea
  - March 21, 1954, Korea
  - March 22, 1954, Korea
  - March 23, 1954, Korea
  - March 25, 1954, Korea
  - March 26, 1954, Korea
  - March 27, 1954, Korea
  - March 28, 1954, Korea
  - March 30, 1954, Korea
  - March 31, 1954, Korea
  - April 2, 1954, Korea (Box 4.)
  - April 3, 1954, Korea
  - April 4, 1954, Korea
  - April 6, 1954, Korea
  - April 7, 1954, Korea
  - April 8, 1954, Korea
  - April 10, 1954, Korea
  - April 11, 1954, Korea
  - April 11, 1954, Korea
  - April 12, 1954, Korea
  - April 13, 1954, Korea
  - April 14, 1954, Korea
  - April 16, 1954, Korea
  - April 17, 1954, Korea
  - April 18, 1954, Korea
  - April 19, 1954, Korea
  - April 21, 1954, Korea
  - April 23, 1954, Korea
  - April 24, 1954, Korea
  - April 25, 1954, Korea
  - April 27, 1954, Korea
  - April 29, 1954, Korea
  - April 30, 1954, Korea
  - May 1, 1954, Korea
  - May 2, 1954, Korea
  - May 3, 1954, Korea
  - May 4, 1954, Korea
  - May 5, 1954, Korea
  - May 7, 1954, Korea
  - May 8, 1954, Korea
  - May 9, 1954, Korea
  - May 11, 1954, Korea
  - May 12, 1954, Korea
  - May 14, 1954, Korea
  - May 16, 1954, Korea
  - May 17, 1954, Korea
  - May 19, 1954, Korea
  - May 20, 1954, Korea
  - May 22, 1954, Korea
  - May 24, 1954, Korea
  - May 25, 1954, Korea
  - May 27, 1954, Korea
  - May 28, 1954, Korea
  - May 30, 1954, Korea
  - May 31, 1954, Korea
  - June 1, 1954, Korea
  - June 2, 1954, Korea
  - June 4, 1954, Korea
  - June 6, 1954, Korea
  - June 6, 1954, Korea
  - June 6, 1954, Korea
  - June 8, 1954, Korea
  - June 11, 1954, Korea
  - June 12, 1954, Korea
  - June 13, 1954, Korea
  - June 16, 1954, Korea
  - June 18, 1954, Korea
  - June 19, 1954, Korea
  - June 20, 1954, Korea
  - June 22, 1954, Korea
  - June 26, 1954, Korea
  - June 28, 1954, Korea
  - June 29, 1954, Korea
  - July 1, 1954, Korea
  - July 3, 1954, Korea
  - July 4, 1954, Korea
  - July 5, 1954, Korea
  - July 7, 1954, Korea
  - July 9, 1954, Korea
  - July 11, 1954, Korea
  - July 13, 1954, Korea
  - July 15, 1954, Korea
  - July 18, 1954, Korea
  - July 18, 1954, Korea
  - July 20, 1954, Korea
  - July 21, 1954, Korea
  - July 23, 1954, Korea
  - July 24, 1954, Korea
  - July 26, 1954, Korea
  - July 30, 1954, Korea
  - August 1, 1954, Korea
  - August 3, 1954, Korea
  - August 3, 1954, Korea
  - August 5, 1954, Korea
  - August 6, 1954, Korea
  - August 8, 1954, Korea
  - August 10, 1954, Korea
  - August 13, 1954, Korea
  - August 14, 1954, Korea
  - August 18, 1954, Korea
  - August 20, 1954, Korea
  - August 23, 1954, Korea
  - August 29, 1954, Korea
  - August 30, 1954, Korea
  - September 1, 1954, Korea
  - September 3, 1954, Korea
  - September 5, 1954, Korea
  - September 7, 1954, Korea
  - September 12, 1954, Korea
  - September 13, 1954, Korea
  - September 16, 1954, Korea
  - September 18, 1954, Korea
  - December 10, 1954, Korea
  - January 18, 1966, Da Nang (Box 5.)
  - January 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 27, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - January 31, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 5, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 12, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 20, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - February 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 1, 1966, Okinawa/Da Nang
  - March 2, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 6, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 11, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 13, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 15, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 17, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 21, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 27, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - March 31, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 2, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 11, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 13, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 15, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 17, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 21, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - April 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 1, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 2, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 4, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 6, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 12, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 15, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 18, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - May 31, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 2, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 4, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 4, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 11, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 12, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 18, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - June 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 2, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 5, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 6, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 11, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 13, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 17, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 21, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 23, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 27, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - July 31, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 1, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 4, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 11, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 13, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 15, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 17, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 21, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 23, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 27, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 28, 1966, Da Nang
  - August 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 1, 1966, Da Nang (Box 6.)
  - September 1, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 10, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 12, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 18, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 19, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 25, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 26, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 27, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - September 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 5, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 8, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 9, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 12, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 14, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 15, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 16, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 17, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 20, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 20, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 21, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 22, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 24, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 26, 1966, Okinawa
  - October 27, 1966, Okinawa
  - October 29, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 30, 1966, Da Nang
  - October 31, 1966, Da Nang
  - November 1, 1966, Da Nang
  - November 3, 1966, Da Nang
  - November 4, 1966, Da Nang
  - November 6, 1966, Da Nang
  - November 7, 1966, Da Nang
  - December 16, 1966, Saigon
  - December 18, 1966, Saigon
  - December 18, 1966, Saigon
  - December 20, 1966, Saigon
  - December 20, 1966, Saigon
  - December 21, 1966, Saigon
  - December 22, 1966, Saigon
  - December 24, 1966, Saigon
  - December 25, 1966, Saigon
  - December 26, 1966, Saigon
  - December 28, 1966, Saigon
  - December 30, 1966, Saigon
  - December 31, 1966, Saigon
  - January 2, 1967, Saigon
  - January 6, 1967, Saigon
  - January 7, 1967, Saigon
  - January 9, 1967, Saigon
  - January 10, 1967, Saigon
  - January 11, 1967, Saigon
  - January 14, 1967, Saigon
  - January 16, 1967, Saigon
  - January 17, 1967, Saigon
  - January 20, 1967, Saigon
  - January 22, 1967, Saigon
  - January 24, 1967, Saigon
  - January 26, 1967, Saigon
  - January 27, 1967, Saigon
  - January 29, 1967, Saigon
  - January 31, 1967, Saigon
  - February 2, 1967, Saigon
  - February 3, 1967, Saigon
  - February 4, 1967, Saigon
  - February 5, 1967, Saigon
  - February 7, 1967, Saigon
  - February 9, 1967, Saigon
  - February 11, 1967, Saigon
  - February 13, 1967, Saigon
  - February 14, 1967, Saigon
  - February 16, 1967, Saigon
  - February 18, 1967, Saigon
  - February 21, 1967, Saigon
  - February 22, 1967, Saigon
  - February 26, 1967, Saigon
  - February 27, 1967, Saigon
  - February 28, 1967, Saigon
  - March 5, 1967, Saigon
  - March 6, 1967, Saigon
  - March 12, 1967, Saigon
  - March 14, 1967, Saigon
  - March 16, 1967, Saigon
  - March 19, 1967, Saigon
  - March 20, 1967, Saigon
  - March 23, 1967, Saigon
  - March 24, 1967, Saigon
  - March 26, 1967, Saigon
  - March 27, 1967, Saigon
  - March 29, 1967, Saigon
  - April 1, 1967, Saigon
  - April 4, 1967, Saigon
  - April 7, 1967, Saigon
  - April 11, 1967, Saigon
  - April 14, 1967, Saigon